Al Nash Collection of Miscellaneous Broadsides 5219
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Al Nash Collection of Miscellaneous Broadsides
1901-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Nash, Abraham (Al)
5219
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Broadsides collected by Abraham (Al) Nash.
5665221
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 25, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Scope and Contents
Broadsides collected by Abraham (Al) Nash.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Labor; Arbitration, Industrial; Shop stewards -- Handbooks, manuals, etc.; Labor unions; Teachers -- Handbooks, manuals, etc.; Automobile industry workers; Socialism; Communism; Collective bargaining -- Handbooks, manuals, etc.; Grievance arbitration; Nash, Al
5665221
- Union newsletters and flyers, ca. 1950s. Socialist Workers Party bulletins, 1940s. Brookwood Labor College Outlines, 1920s. GM-UAW contract material, 1930s and 1940s.. (Box 1)
  - Published by Unions, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Grievance Procedures, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - UAW-GM Department - Educational Outline - Covering terms of the National Agreement - Leonard Woodcock, Vice President UAW and Director UAW GM Department, 1955- 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Misc. #5219, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Brookwood, 1925-1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brookwood, 1925-1929 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Brookwood, 1925-1929 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Internal Bulletin of the Socialist Workers Party, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Stalinist Russia: A Bureaucratic Collectivist Society, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ria Stone, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Internal Bulletin Socialist Workers Party, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bulletin Number 1 Active Workers Conference, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bulletin number 1. Active Workers Conference, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Socialist Workers Party bulletins, resolutions, educational material, meeting agendas, 1930s, 1940s, and 1950s. Includes reports by party branches within the UAW, literary journals, and city election materials.. (Box 2)
  - Resolution of the Minority on the Negro Question by J.R. Johnson (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The State, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Tenants Work, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - War and Tech. Develop. Building Bolshevik Party (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Burocratic Jungle (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Declaration of the Resolution on the United States, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Principles and Practices of Organization (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Role of Trade Unions Transitional Program, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Role of Trade Unios: Their Economic Role Under Capitalism (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Workers Party of U.S.A., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bulletins and Forums, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Worker's Party, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bulletins of the Worker's Party, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bulletins of the Workers Party, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bulletins of the Worker's Party, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bulletin of the Worker's Party, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Student Anti-War publications, 1950s Socialist Party Educational Materials, 1940s Bulletin of the Workers Party, vol.1 no ~ 1-20; 1940s Party Builder - Workers Party, vol II no 1-4, vol 3 no 1; 1940s Politics, Socialist Party journal, March 1944 - April 1 (Box 3)
  - W.P. Bulletins - 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Party Bulletins, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Politics, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Worker's Party Papers, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Worker's Party, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bulletin of the Workers Party Contents, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bulletin of the Workers Party, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins of the Workers Party, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bulletin's of the Worker's Party, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bulletins of the Worker's Party, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Worker's Party, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - A Student Anti War Quarterly; Anvil, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 12)